<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[It's a MAN's World]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[It's a MAN's World]]></description>
        <link>http://itsamans.world/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 03:11:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://itsamans.world/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 03:11:27 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who We Are Here For…]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Who We Are Here For…</h1>,<p>This is a site for guys to get what guys want, from places they can relate to, and based on good information. And it’s about just being a guy.</p>,<p>This is a site for guys to get what guys want, from places they can relate to, and based on good information. And it’s about just being a guy.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/402c22d2-e86a-42d8-a150-882bfbefa289.jpg">,<p><em>Daddy like! In the world of home workshops this is what would be known as a wet dream.</em></p>,<p><em>Daddy like! In the world of home workshops this is what would be known as a wet dream.</em></p>,<p>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~</p>,<p>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~</p>,<p>Someday soon you’ll be standing in your driveway, after work, talking to your neighbor.</p>,<p>Someday soon you’ll be standing in your driveway, after work, talking to your neighbor.</p>,<p>You: <em>Yeah, went to Man’s World today. Bought a hyphendoophenator. Nice one. Three-speed, self-attenuating…all the bells and whistles.</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Yeah, went to Man’s World today. Bought a hyphendoophenator. Nice one. Three-speed, self-attenuating…all the bells and whistles.</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>Was the flux capacitor standard?</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>Was the flux capacitor standard?</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Yep.</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Yep.</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>How good is the whodaddy attachment?</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>How good is the whodaddy attachment?</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Perfect!</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Perfect!</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>Damn. I got my hyphendoophenator at Lowe’s. The only thing it comes with is an automatic nose picker and a cup holder. And the whodaddy is made of plastic!</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>Damn. I got my hyphendoophenator at Lowe’s. The only thing it comes with is an automatic nose picker and a cup holder. And the whodaddy is made of plastic!</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Yeah, well, I told you to go to Man’s World, didn’t I?</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Yeah, well, I told you to go to Man’s World, didn’t I?</em></p>,<p>We will create a page for you, where ever you are in the market, for anything we can find to make your life better. We’ll start with tools and add on from there. We will source information for the best stuff at different price points and feature them. We hope to save you a lot of headaches when buying. Did you catch that? I didn’t say shopping. Men don’t shop. They buy.</p>,<p>We will create a page for you, where ever you are in the market, for anything we can find to make your life better. We’ll start with tools and add on from there. We will source information for the best stuff at different price points and feature them. We hope to save you a lot of headaches when buying. Did you catch that? I didn’t say shopping. Men don’t shop. They buy.</p>,<p>But you need good intel, and we will do our best to provide just that.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxlztEKgjAYBeBXGd63f2kpE5NA6DJ6g1jz143aJttQevuc0EV0eeCcj3NTLjrSeex1rEkjiPI4nDIV4xRqgGVZ6PDS8umpdAam1A7A-ZHzsijOV8agKit2yNk-Z5C1JlpEfzfCNiBactmmZNbil17llZsGPaqY4KztvnHb_f2QHkXUM65d42ygzo-w2mgDBni8d7aHnKYDUibgA4dIRto" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/who-we-are-here-for/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bc30ab32-0cd0-4bf1-bbbe-9a49ef208188</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 20:46:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Eye Within the Eye]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Eye Within the Eye</h1>,<h2>A good photo</h2>,<p>There is something about a quality photograph that really speaks to us.</p>,<p>I know a few good photographers. And I know that if we stood shoulder-to-shoulder with identical cameras and snapped pictures of the same kid we get different results. People would look at my photos and say, “Look. cute kid.”</p>,<p>But from a photographer with a gift, they’d say something like, “I just can't stop looking at this kid. Look her eyes! You can just sense…” Or, “The eyes practically reach out of the picture…”</p>,<p>I’ve heard people say that the secret to good photography is lighting or composition or some other technical aspect. I can tell you first hand that’s not so. I’ve taken thousands of pictures in my lifetime and few actually exude life.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3d5311a5-e169-4ae8-a651-8edf5f78e2fc.jpg">,<p>No doubt, those things are important. But there is far more to it.</p>,<p>People like <a href="http://kathleenroche.wixsite.com/photo" title="">Kathleen Roche</a> have that innate ability to give a photograph life. I envy them.</p>,<p>I use her work here and hope to do so more on the future.</p>,<p>But among the hobbies, habits and passions one may pursue, one that can bring real satisfaction as well as tangible results would have to be photography.</p>,<p>Tom Jordan, a photographer from Pennsylvania, says the he goes out and just walks. It could be on the beach, or in Philadelphia or in his favorite park (location secret) and he says, “I don’t know what I’m going to get, or where I’m going to get it, but I know that day I’m going to really nail a picture.” </p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxljtEKgjAYhV9l-AD7ly3NMAmELqNXWPPXjdJ_bEPp7ZtCF9HlgfN959wNRWKtx87GE6sVMx77c2ZidOEEsCwL719WPz3XNIJb2wFkUUl52BWXmxCwF1JWVZGXxxyyxmHnKdiRMJQ1qIZdN5rNVv3akzwZXW8HE1d31rTfuHF_V7RHFe2MqTvSFDj5AZIbp4ABHm_IuUj7Wm_0B8D6RvE" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/the-eye-within-the-eye/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6e63d16a-385a-435d-9017-383087d12857</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 19:47:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Passions, Hobbies and Pursuits]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Passions, Hobbies and Pursuits</h1>,<h3><strong>Photography</strong></h3>,<p><a href="http://itsamans.world/the-eye-within-the-eye" title="">The Eye Within The Eye</a></p>,<h3><strong>Cigar Aficionado</strong></h3>,<p><a href="http://itsamans.world/the-cigars-series" title="">Cigars</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/hobbies-and-pursuits/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a19f7c6d-a528-4c2f-9366-578e43b05784</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 21:21:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is a Man?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>What is a Man?</h1>,<p>There is an image of what Americans see as manhood that isn’t <strong>quite</strong> uniquely American, but it’s close.</p>,<p>In a world where we are constantly being pitted, one group of people against another, we are sometimes expected to apologize for who we are. This website will never subscribe to the homogenized view of what people are supposed to be. BUT…There are qualities that identify us and they shouldn't be scoffed at.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cda046e5-8625-475e-a4c9-6a82b5ba424e.jpg">,<p>Here, we celebrate what people are. And in this case we celebrate the strong, American male role model.</p>,<p>The man we celebrate teaches his kids early the value of a dollar, respect for property, reading for enjoyment and love of competition. He exposes them to his passions and interest. Of course, he hopes they’ll adopt them. But what is important is that they develop their own.</p>,<p>He exudes strength in whatever capacity he possesses it; through whatever talents and abilities he’s developed. He takes quiet pleasure in a job well-done.</p>,<p>The REAL American man says “thank you” to kindnesses. He greets people confidently and happily. He leaves a room, a crowd, a campsite and his planet better off than the way he found it; even if only in small measure.</p>,<p>He isn’t arrogant. He loves easily. He beams with pride at his kids. His son makes him want to measure up. His daughter OWNS him.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/aec9e9a1-246f-48e3-b12a-a23b001c8879.jpg">,<p>If he is smart, a part of what motivates him to fix a light switch, replace a pipe, paint a wall, or head out to work everyday, is his desire to show off for the woman he loves.</p>,<p>This is the man our site is dedicated to.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9dcb3c7c-752a-4a15-bf93-b729bc7b8a2f.jpg">,<p>Photo credit: <a href="http://kathleenroche.wixsite.com/photo" title="">http://kathleenroche.wixsite.com/photo</a></p>,<p><a href="http://itsamans.world/but-not-every-guy-is-married-with-kids" title="">But Not every guy is married with kids!</a></p>,<p>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~</p>,<p>The pictures in this article gave me a thought. This website will use advertising to keep the lights on. And we will make the ads content appropriate. We won’t put an ad for an iPad in a post about chain saws.</p>,<p>Anyway, the thought. Tools kits for kids. One of the most important things I think I missed as a kid was familiarity with proper tools and their uses, and mechanical experience. I learned much of it in the Navy and I am a self-taught furniture maker. But I’d have been much further ahead of the game as a young man if someone had mentored me in <em>any</em> of the trades.</p>,<p>So here are some suggestion for bringing kids into the trades in a fun way. By “playing” with your son or daughter, going through the motions of using play tools, you not only engage them in a learning activity, you create a bond around that activity.</p>,<h2>For the Toddler:</h2>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkUFv2zAMhe_7FYEPuqVWHDdxu6pDhwHtBgwdEGxXgZZoR4sluRRTL_v1c5QW2DuJj9SnB-rOdQQeF4lPA6picpb3t6tKjn8-7tH1e76t6nNRLDxQ70IeUIV8ry9D2UiG4jC40KsixGKRuW0ki3Rpk1FFWU5pGeAKPPyNYQk2nRKjvzLRlzO6R07ly6cd0qsz-AspuRhUJeVWNlUlngN-26mVeB6RgM-tR-QH-8R-EN-BDsg_BjCofu5EikeaT2AEYae40-wGAVbzaUQ1UrRHw3oOexBMYA5zau2s8sC_Iy0rKXzGjRl3CTuD-vOTMzzbHgOrz3L1UO--rBopILmQ_jfO9K9WYd3AWm5N3dZd09xsO7ttrjebFuR1C3Z9I9I-TvptUR0MCfNNHUcMSbugA056csHGSTEdUYw070abOERS6yzBjod3S8rNxkjR9m91l1Xcf1jMuisv_33_D-41rgQ" height="244"></iframe>,<p>I chose this kit because it had a good variety of tools and some hardware. It makes the use of the tools less abstract over time. It will be easier to keep a kid angaged by “fixing” lots of things in different ways.</p>,<p>HOWEVER!!!</p>,<p>If you are Harley guy, and there are lots of you out there, there’s always this kit:</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkctu2zAQRff5CkML7hxRjB05aZiiQR5NgSItjHZL0ORIZs2HMhxXdb--Mp0AvSvOneHhxfDGdagDzDIdPMhqdJa2143gw58PW3D9lq7F4lhUs6Cxd7EMyIq_16ehYmSDyXsXe1nFVM0Kd5PQAp7aaGRV12OeR32ug_6b4lzbfMgE4dykUE_oHijXrx_XgL-dgZ-A2aUoBectXwnBXiJ8WcuGvQyAmo6tJ6BP9jMFz75q3AF989qA_LFmOe1xOmnDEDpJnSLnmbaKDgPIAZPdG1JT2B0j1GY3pVbOyqDpV8K54CwU3FBwp7ATqD8-OcGLHSCSvOPN_dXq8eHqO9PZxfy_caQ_W7lcNBemaxZt25olF60A2Jh2IVYrvhTLlrO8TaN6W1SnfYZyU6UBYlYuqgijGl20aZSEe2ADTrtRJvmE8qKIkSP_bnF-eWk42_RvdVdU3Z7NJt3Up_--_Qea7q1M" height="244"></iframe>,<p>There’s not as many pieces, but damn! It’s a Harley kit!</p>,<p>Either way, by using toys like this, as well as doctor kits and crayons, you can immerse yourself in you own kid’s world. Let him imitate and then lead, go back and forth. If you are a first time father you will be amazed at what you learn about your son or daughter as you do this. And they will love you for it.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/what-is-a-man/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c533441e-bce8-4eb4-a4f5-53b1c3522dad</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 20:51:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[…But Not Every Guy is Married With Kids.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>…But Not Every Guy is Married With Kids.</h1>,<p><em><strong>“A man doesn't have time in his life<br> to have time for everything.<br> He doesn't have seasons enough to have<br> a season for every purpose. Ecclesiastes<br> Was wrong about that.”</strong></em></p>,<p>That’s an excerpt from the excellent poem <em>A Man in His Life</em> by Yehuda Amichai. It, among other works, are among the things all young men should read. It makes the clear point that life is about decisions and actions that must be taken, regardless of what life brings you.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e39a65d0-7d08-42ac-8e05-5b4c6fc2441b.jpg">,<p>A single man is every bit as burdened or blessed by these challenges as the married man. The idea that being single is a picnic is an illusion. While the partnered father may have the burden of protecting and providing for others, the motivation to do so is provided him, in that those people exist.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/52a83a83-fa03-46b3-b3eb-4529800580e8.jpg">,<p>The single man must make his life, and find success and maturity through his own motivation; under his own head of steam. If he makes excuses, he makes them to ether. He cannot measure success by the love and gratitude in the eyes of others. He can only measure it through harsh self-assessment.</p>,<p>Does he have greater freedom? Of course. But he has no counterweight to help him modulate how he enjoys that freedom. He only has his own ambition and his own conscience to guide him.</p>,<p>It is as a single man he should develop his passions. If his work is his passion, he is lucky indeed, but even that isn’t enough to round him out and allow him to make the most of his world. A few days hiking the Appalachian Trail or working wood into a desk or repairing a small engine will help him to take on his professional or trade challanges afresh for the following week.</p>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/95184b24843201b63240e7a992299c76/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=3426&cropwidth=4904&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fs3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fthe-grid-img%2Fp%2F9951dc6d9a6f3a243f620c09c929656abfedc806.jpg&x=30&y=0">,<p>And of course, unless he intends to remain single, he must balance his freedom and maneuverability against the possibility of attracting his soul mate. This is the hardest and most critical task of all.</p>,<p>Man Ironing</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxljtEKgjAYhV9leN9-XVNSTAyhq4heYa3pRrrJNpTevs3oIro88J3vnJs03qDOiofyFaoZklb0x0R6P7sKYF1X3I-KPy3mZoI50g7KoqBpVh7aa0qBlDQnGdnnJYWkOWlvlBaXD9kOE1NjrNbAGnTeTGhR7HcpDAVk7tUgfYSTpvvGrfd3i1vBvFpEYCejHTZ2gOAW2gkH99dO851jQHAaHnEeHW_zok1d" height="244"></iframe>,<p>Hoodie</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxlztEKwiAYBeBXkd3P39kijTWCQZfRK5hzU9pUVDZ6-9ygi-jywDkf56FdcqgLqjfpjBqBdFDDpdAp-XgGWNcVD5ORr4Clm8Fv7Qic8ZoSSq53QuBQsYqfas6ONRStdl5NKsaKsgZEi277GC1G_OLZzqAfzKjTRhdt94377u-JDEoks6jcnZ2N2IURsq1sVBGe79LK0vZAMcknpNyMD6BKR-s" height="244"></iframe>,<p>Man in a suit</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxlztEKgyAYBeBXke7n76xJRYtBsMuxV3BqKSsNlaK3nwW7GLs8cM7HeWoXHeq8kibWqOFIe9VfMx3jHGqAdV1xPxrx9li4Cea9HeBMqqJklyq_PQiFnDBWspJQWkDWcjmqDWu-rc7JBniL7sceLYb_-olP5tybQcddz9ruG4_d3xnhFY9mUak7ORuw8wMkW9mgAry2kxUnK4Fikm4IsRsfqjhJVA" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/but-not-every-guy-is-married-with-kids/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5d30d091-ca53-4364-9c90-f48add0fa411</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 20:52:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tool Kits (ages 7-11)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Tool Kits (ages 7-11)</h1>,<p>So your child isn’t a toddler anymore. If he enjoyed his first toy tool kit, you may consider upping the game a bit. I looked at what is on the market and these items jumped out at me.</p>,<p>Amazon sometimes shows them as a combination if you pull up the woodworking kit. This kit is amazing. I have three grandchildren, a girl and two boys, one featured in the post <em><a href="http://itsamans.world/what-is-a-man" title="">What Is A Man?</a>, </em>who will soon be ready for this. Shy of having your kids work in the shop on real projects (that could get a bit dodgy), I can’t think of a better way to teach them the basics.</p>,<p>Note: The younger they are the more you’ll have to remind them that tools and lumber can’t be left around. That’s “dangerous” and can ruin a good project. “Besides”, you might say, “This is how <em><strong>real</strong></em> carpenters take care of their stuff.”</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkU9vEzEQxe98imgPvqXr7rabUOoiEBIUCaVSBBIna2LPbkz8ZxlPWNJPz8ZpJd7J82b889P43vUEAReZTx5VNTnL-7vrRo5_3-3RDXu-a27ORbUIQIOLZUBV8rW-DBUjG0reuzioKqZqUbi7RBbp0iajqrqe8jLCFQR4TnEJNp8yY7gyKdQzekDO9e_3W6Q_zuAPpOxSVI2UK7luGrGJ-HWrrsVmRAI-tz4jf7BfOHjxDeiA_OTBoPq-FTkdaT6BEYS94l6z8wKs5tOIaqRkj4b1HPYgmMAc5tTaWRWAfyVaNlKEghsL7hJ2Bg3nJ2d4sQNGVh-lfPv489PqaSMgu5j_N870R6v6FladsXJ323fdykIHuGvbZn2z7kzTt7ci79OkXxbVg89Ybuo0YszaRR1x0pOLNk2K6YhipHk32iSfSLVFgh37V0vKrjNS7IaXui-qHt4sZt3Xl_9--Adve67E" height="244"></iframe>,<p>Here’s a tool kit that is an obvious step up from plactic hammers, but sized and designed for young hands.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkU1vGyEQhu_9FdYeuDmLiWPni1TppUmkypEs94owDGtiPrbDOBv313eNE6nviXlneHg13HuHOsKk0DGAbAZvaXc7E7z_uNuB73Z0K-anoplEjZ1PdUA2_Ks-D1WjGMwh-NTJJuVmUrnbjBbw3EYjm7YdyjTpCx3135ym2pZjIYgXJsd2RHdApf3zfQ347g38Biw-Jyk4X_JrIdgqwctaztiqB9R0av0EerRPFAP7pXEP9Bq0AblZs5IPOJ60YQhOklPkA9NW0bEH2WO2B0NqDLtnhNrsx9TKWxk1vWWcCs5ixfUVdw47grrTkyO82hESyR-czx6fN2KzYrr4VP43TvRnK831zeWNmAs7X7qrhbmyzjjuDOdiubWCa1Z2eVCfi3I6FKg3Ve4hFeWTSjCowSebB0l4ANbjuBtlcsgoL6sYeQpfFueLheFs233Wrqp5-DYZdd-e__vhH0y9rp4" height="244"></iframe>,<p>OR</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkU1vEzEQhu_8imgPvqXrLGibtHURcKBFgiJF9GpN7NmNiT-W8YQl_Hocp5UYX_y-M348Ht-5gSDgIvPJo2pmZ3l_s-rk9Od2j27c80337iyaRQAaXawFqpGv-lJUjWwoee_iqJqYmkXl7hJZpEuajGrads7LCFcQ4G-KS7D5lBnDlUmhLegRObe_3m-RfjuDz0jZpag6Ka_luuvEU8QvW7USTxMS8Dn1GfmDfeDgxVegA_J3DwbVj63I6UhlB0YQDooHzc4LsJpPE6qJkj0a1qXZg2ACcyhda2dVAP6ZaNlJESpuqrhLswU0nq8s8GoHjKw-SrnefHv89LAWkF3M_xtn-qNVIFfXG1lGurMb6LsiNqYsxJ0xfV9elfdp1i-DGsBnrCd1mjBm7aKOOOvZRZtmxXREMVGZjTbJJ1Jvawh27F8tKfveSLEbX_RQo7l_syhx117--_4f90auCw" height="244"></iframe>,<p>Why should I leave my baby girl out, right?</p>,<h2>Okay…Here’s a two-fer. Help spur their love of reading while teaching them how to use plans to execute successful projects.</h2>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkcFu2zAMhu97isAH3VIrauykXdWip7UFhg4IuqtAS7SjRZY8iamXPf0UpQXGE_mT-viDurN9hBEXiU4OZTVbQ_vbleDTn697tMOebsX6XFSLEeJgfRmQFf-sL0NFSDoG56wfZOVDtSjcLkSD8dKOWlZ1PaelhysY4W_wSzDplAjHKx3GOqMHpFT_fthhfLcaf2JMNngpON_wrRDs1ePLTq7Y64QR6Nz6hvRonmh07DvEA9IPBxrl246lcIw5A80i9pJ6RdYxMIpOE8opBnPUpLLZA6MI-pBdK2vkCPQrxKXgbCy4qeAuZjNoOK_M8CKP6Eny9bYVDW82KwbJ-vS_cKY_G9k1TStE291s4Rq2je70JqebFltYQ9fesLQPs_o4VA8uYXmpwoQ-KeuVx1nN1pswS4pHZFPMt1E6uBDldQlGltynxHnbas664aPuS1T3XxY57urLf9__A5EsrX0" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/tool-kits-ages-7-11/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">64e8435a-73f7-4b57-ba80-020d09140873</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 02:55:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cigars:  A Brief History (Conclusion)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Cigars:  A Brief History (Conclusion)</h1>,<p>With the cigar market undergoing radical change, the industry was remade. In 2000, General Cigar closed its Jamaica factory, ending some 30 years of history and putting an end to Jamaica’s era as a cigar-industry power (it had ranked third among major
shippers in the early 1990s). Cigar shipments from Mexico, also once vibrant,
have shrunk yearly, from 11 million in 1998 to fewer than 1 million last year.
Nicaragua is the new star of the cigar world, with shipments growing
continuously since 2003. The nation’s cigars, once embargoed in the U.S.
market, have soared from 33 million in 2003 to 102 million last year, vaulting
to second place among premium cigar producers. The shift is a sign of the
changing tastes of connoisseurs, who are flocking to the fuller flavors of Nicaraguan tobacco.</p>,<p>Cigar imports have since recovered from the post-boom years. In 2001, they began to climb again—albeit at a far slower rate— and between that year and 2011 imports have
increased by an average of six percent annually, with more than 278 million
cigars imported last year—approaching three times the size of the cigar market
in 1992, on a unit basis.</p>,<p>Today, the myriad companies that make, market, distribute and retail cigars worry not about who will buy their cigars, but if the government will cripple the industry with
over regulation and taxes. The possibility that the Food and Drug
Administration will slap restrictions on the industry, increasingly higher
taxes and fewer and fewer cigar-friendly venues are the worries of the moment,
and some fear that the government could ruin the cigar business.</p>,<p>But the legacy of the cigar boom can be seen in the heir apparents to some of the world’s most famous cigar brands. <br>
Children of cigar makers, who had nearly forsaken their birthrights in the
industry, were once again emboldened to join their parents. Today the cigar
business is rich with father/son, father/daughter, brother/brother and
brother/sister teams, including the Fuentes, Padróns, Quesadas, Eiroas,
Garcias, Patels, Levins, Kelners, Newmans, Plasencias, Turrents, two Oliva
families (one growing leaf, one making cigars) and many more. Charlie Toraño
abandoned his law practice and joined his father in 1996, and today is
president of the company, becoming the fourth generation in his family in the
tobacco business.</p>,<p>Today Quesada proudly sits at the helm of MATASA, albeit in a new, far larger and more modern cigar factory, with his two daughters, Raquel and Patricia, taking an increasingly
active role in the company, along with a number of nephews, nieces and cousins.
They make blends using leaves that weren’t grown in the 1980s, package the
cigars in vibrant boxes with modern logos and use their Blackberries to tweet
about the products to cigar lovers around the world.</p>,<p>Twenty years ago, cigar makers toiled in obscurity in a business that few felt had any future. “Nobody knew who was behind the products,” says retailer Gary Pesh. Today, cigar makers are stars, similar to celebrity chefs. And while cigar sales today aren’t
nearly as vibrant as they were during the peak of the boom, the cigar market is
far larger today than it was before the boom. Premium cigar imports in 2011
(the last full year available) were 278.5 million cigars, well more than
two-and-a-half times their level in 1991, when only 103.6 million cigars were
imported.</p>,<p>While the market for cigars is far larger on a unit scale, the impact of the past 20 years is far more pronounced when you look at the overall value of the market. The average
price for a premium cigar in 1990 was $1.75, according to Cigar Insider
estimates, giving the U.S. premium cigar industry a market value of $186
million. The average price of a cigar rose to $3.23 by 1996, giving the market
a value of close to $1 billion.</p>,<p>Today, cigar prices have pushed even higher. While there are bargains to be found, most lie in the $5 to $7 range. Many cigars sell for around $10, and special cigars push the
upper limits of premium cigar pricing to $25, $30 and more per cigar. <br>
The average retail price of a premium cigar rated by either Cigar Aficionado or
Cigar Insider in 2012 is $9.51. At that average price, the U.S. premium cigar
market would have a value of $2.6 billion—14 times the value of the annual
market in 1990.</p>,<p>The cigar world has been completely, unforgettably transformed. Cigar makers work alongside their sons and daughters, and no one who makes a cigar in 2012 worries that consumers down the road will lose interest in their product.</p>,<p>“Thank God for the cigar boom,” says Carlos Fuente Jr., one of the icons of the cigar business. “For the first time in history, tobacco farmers, tobacco dealers, people who
own smoke shops were all able to make a decent living.”</p>,<p><em>Jim Sass is a highly regarded mentor and business consultant.  You can find some of his work below.  Like many successful people, Sass has a few passions.  Among those are Harleys, good scotch and fine cigars.  </em></p>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/760fe3fe12d750a8d7b0954ca977fabf/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=3000&cropwidth=2253&degrees=-270&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fc304427b-6a6b-4afa-bf22-bcfafb1336b7.jpg&x=0&y=0" alt="Source:  Jim Sass">]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/cigars-a-brief-history-conclusion/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e5a96f41-f083-4a67-a50e-24351bacc880</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 03:11:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cigars:  A Brief History (Part 3)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Cigars:  A Brief History (Part 3)</strong></h1>,<h2><strong>The Boom Continues</strong></h2>,<p>As cigar sales grew, so did the girth (measured in ring gauge) of the most-popular smokes. One retailer said that in 1990, almost 80 percent of his sales came from the very
slim lonsdales and coronas sizes. By 1996, most of his sales came from fat
robustos and corona gordas. The first edition of <em>Cigar Aficionado</em>
magazine rated 17 robustos, the fattest of which had a ring gauge of 52. The
Diamond Crown brand, a line consisting entirely of 54-ring gauge cigars, made
news in 1995 when it was launched—as 54s were considered quite thick in those
days. Today, a ring gauge of 60 characterizes one of the most popular sizes in
American smoke shops.</p>,<p>The effects of the cigar boom reached Cuba as well. Consumers flocked to Cuban cigar stores and bought every cigar they could find. On a trip to Havana in early 1996, the <em>Cigar Aficionado</em> editors visited nine cigar shops and couldn’t find a double
corona, Montecristo No. 2 or Partagás Serie D No. 4. Cuba, which had produced
fewer than 60 million export-quality cigars in 1993 and 1994, vastly increased
its production. Cuban cigar exports reached 100 million units in 1997, and
officials announced the long-term goal of increasing further to 200 million
cigars by the year 2000.</p>,<p>In November 1996, Cuba launched the Cuaba brand, the first new brand from the island in nearly 30 years. That was soon followed by such creations as Vegas Robaina, Trinidad and San Cristobal de la Habana. Cuba opened new cigar factories and vastly
increased plantings of tobacco. Alas, the mandate to pump out cigars at such a
rate resulted in a rash of inferior product.</p>,<p>Wall Street soon took an interest in cigars, and six cigar companies went public in 1996. Newcomer Caribbean Cigar Co. became the first stand-alone public cigar company with its August 1, 1996 initial public offering. Sixteen days later, high-profile
financier Ronald Perelman took his Consolidated Cigar Holdings public for $23 a
share. Machine-made giant Swisher International Group Inc., the cigar retailers
JR and Holts, and even a one-year-old company named Tamboril soon followed
suit.</p>,<p>By 1995, more than 25 million cigars were on back order, and in 1996, that number was more than 50 million. Cigar brands such as Arturo Fuente and La Gloria Cubana became
impossible to find. For six weeks of the summer of 1996, General Cigar didn’t
ship a single Macanudo cigar, the best-selling premium cigar in the United
States at the time. “We were using tobacco so rapidly we got caught. We didn’t
have enough in the aging blend,” said then-company president Austin T. McNamara.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/cigars-a-brief-history-part-3/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8f0e23ab-a933-414f-aecd-49f7b4ea6af6</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 02:37:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Cigars Series]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Cigars Series</h1>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJzLKCkpsNLXzywpTsxNzCvWK88vyknRT85MTywq1k3UTSrKTE3TzcgsLskvqtQtSCwq0TUEAPG_Evs" height="244"></iframe>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJzLKCkpsNLXzywpTsxNzCvWK88vyknRT85MTywq1k3UTSrKTE3TzcgsLskvqtQtSCwq0TUCAPHAEvw" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/the-cigars-series/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">314e87db-5d2e-425a-9d53-cee60ead2178</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cigars: A Brief History (Part 2)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Cigars: A Brief History (Part 2)</h1>,<h2>The Industry Adjusts to the New Reality</h2>,<p>“When we got the embargo, we bought tobacco left and right by telephone,” said Alfons Mayer in 2002. Mayer, who died in 2006, spent years as the main tobacco buyer for General Cigar Co. “We were buying Puerto Rican, Dominican, Colombian, people went to Brazil, we went all over Honduras, our native tobaccos here [in the United States], we used some Java, some air cured, we made blends, blends, blends. People went to different areas to try and grow tobacco. There was a lot of trial and error.”</p>,<p>Cuba’s exiled cigar makers traveled far and wide searching for new places to roll. The Menendez family went to the Canary Islands to make cigars, and soon launched Montecruz, a copy of the Montecristo brand it had lost in Cuba. General Cigar turned to Jamaica, where cigar making had been a big business during the Second World War. General acquired the Temple Hall Factory in 1969, which included a then-unknown brand named Macanudo, destined to become the best-selling premium cigar in the United States for many years.</p>,<p>Many of Cuba’s exiled cigar makers made deals with American cigar companies to license or sell their cigar brand names, resulting in non-Cuban versions of Partagás, Punch, H. Upmann, Hoyo de Monterrey, Montecristo and other cigars strictly sold in the United States. The landmark 1972 lawsuit Menendez v. Faber, Coe &amp; Gregg established a legal precedent in which the rights of the owners to sell their non-Cuban versions were upheld by American law.</p>,<p>Tobacco seeds were brought around the world, and propagated in various countries. French tobacco monopoly SEITA established plantations in Cameroon in western Africa in the late 1950s. The rich, toothy wrapper became an industry favorite, and the Meerapfel family saved it from extinction after the French left Africa in the early 1960s. At that time tobacco pioneers had success planting Cuban seeds in Honduras. In 1967, Carlos Toraño Sr. brought Cuban seeds to the Dominican Republic, a nation just removed from civil war, and helped improve the quality of the country’s tobacco, which was mostly grown for cigarettes at the time.</p>,<p>With Dominican Republic cigars currently ubiquitous, it may be hard for a modern-day cigar lover to believe that 40 years ago the Dominican Republic made very few cigars for export. In the 1970s, most of the imported cigars enjoyed in the United States were rolled in the Canary Islands, Jamaica and Mexico, and America still made a large number of cigars. In the early 1970s, free-trade zones opened in the Dominican Republic. Conglomerate Gulf + Western, then the owner of Consolidated Cigar Corp., a company that later became Altadis U.S.A. Inc., began processing tobacco in La Romana in 1969 and started rolling cigars there in 1972.</p>,<p>In 1974 a free-trade zone opened in Santiago, and Manufactura de Tabacos S.A., known as MATASA, soon set up shop. Its owner, Manuel Quesada, explained in a 2004 interview in <em>Cigar Aficionado</em>: “In Miami, the cigar makers that had come out of Cuba were getting older, and with the Social Security a lot of them had to be paid under the table and it started to become a hassle. The free zones had just started in the Dominican Republic. So it was a good idea to transfer production from Miami to the Dominican Republic.”</p>,<p>By the mid-1980s, the Dominican Republic was a hot spot for making cigars. In the 1990s, it became the center of the cigar universe.</p>,<p>Imports of premium, handmade cigars began to climb towards the end of 1992—soon after <em>Cigar Aficionado</em> magazine appeared in September of that year. The American cigar market was turned on its head, and would go through a period of unimaginable growth. Premium cigar imports rose by 3.7 percent in 1992, 9.7 percent in 1993, 12.4 percent in 1994, 33.1 percent in 1995 and soared 66.7 percent in 1996, to more than 293 million cigars. Between 1992 and 1996, the market for fine cigars nearly tripled.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/cigars-a-brief-history-part-2/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">82aaf6af-ce5a-42af-97d0-4293f79ee900</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 23:07:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>