<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[It's a MAN's World]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[It's a MAN's World]]></description>
        <link>http://itsamans.world/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 03:27:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://itsamans.world/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 03:26:59 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Eye Within the Eye]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Eye Within the Eye</h1>,<h2>A good photo</h2>,<p>There is something about a quality photograph that really speaks to us.</p>,<p>I know a few good photographers. And I know that if we stood shoulder-to-shoulder with identical cameras and snapped pictures of the same kid we get different results. People would look at my photos and say, “Look. cute kid.”</p>,<p>But from a photographer with a gift, they’d say something like, “I just can't stop looking at this kid. Look her eyes! You can just sense…” Or, “The eyes practically reach out of the picture…”</p>,<p>I’ve heard people say that the secret to good photography is lighting or composition or some other technical aspect. I can tell you first hand that’s not so. I’ve taken thousands of pictures in my lifetime and few actually exude life.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3d5311a5-e169-4ae8-a651-8edf5f78e2fc.jpg">,<p>No doubt, those things are important. But there is far more to it.</p>,<p>People like <a href="http://kathleenroche.wixsite.com/photo" title="">Kathleen Roche</a> have that innate ability to give a photograph life. I envy them.</p>,<p>I use her work here and hope to do so more on the future.</p>,<p>But among the hobbies, habits and passions one may pursue, one that can bring real satisfaction as well as tangible results would have to be photography.</p>,<p>Tom Jordan, a photographer from Pennsylvania, says the he goes out and just walks. It could be on the beach, or in Philadelphia or in his favorite park (location secret) and he says, “I don’t know what I’m going to get, or where I’m going to get it, but I know that day I’m going to really nail a picture.” </p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxljtEKgjAYhV9l-AD7ly3NMAmELqNXWPPXjdJ_bEPp7ZtCF9HlgfN959wNRWKtx87GE6sVMx77c2ZidOEEsCwL719WPz3XNIJb2wFkUUl52BWXmxCwF1JWVZGXxxyyxmHnKdiRMJQ1qIZdN5rNVv3akzwZXW8HE1d31rTfuHF_V7RHFe2MqTvSFDj5AZIbp4ABHm_IuUj7Wm_0B8D6RvE" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/the-eye-within-the-eye/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6e63d16a-385a-435d-9017-383087d12857</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 19:47:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is a Man?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>What is a Man?</h1>,<p>There is an image of what Americans see as manhood that isn’t <strong>quite</strong> uniquely American, but it’s close.</p>,<p>In a world where we are constantly being pitted, one group of people against another, we are sometimes expected to apologize for who we are. This website will never subscribe to the homogenized view of what people are supposed to be. BUT…There are qualities that identify us and they shouldn't be scoffed at.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cda046e5-8625-475e-a4c9-6a82b5ba424e.jpg">,<p>Here, we celebrate what people are. And in this case we celebrate the strong, American male role model.</p>,<p>The man we celebrate teaches his kids early the value of a dollar, respect for property, reading for enjoyment and love of competition. He exposes them to his passions and interest. Of course, he hopes they’ll adopt them. But what is important is that they develop their own.</p>,<p>He exudes strength in whatever capacity he possesses it; through whatever talents and abilities he’s developed. He takes quiet pleasure in a job well-done.</p>,<p>The REAL American man says “thank you” to kindnesses. He greets people confidently and happily. He leaves a room, a crowd, a campsite and his planet better off than the way he found it; even if only in small measure.</p>,<p>He isn’t arrogant. He loves easily. He beams with pride at his kids. His son makes him want to measure up. His daughter OWNS him.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/aec9e9a1-246f-48e3-b12a-a23b001c8879.jpg">,<p>If he is smart, a part of what motivates him to fix a light switch, replace a pipe, paint a wall, or head out to work everyday, is his desire to show off for the woman he loves.</p>,<p>This is the man our site is dedicated to.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9dcb3c7c-752a-4a15-bf93-b729bc7b8a2f.jpg">,<p>Photo credit: <a href="http://kathleenroche.wixsite.com/photo" title="">http://kathleenroche.wixsite.com/photo</a></p>,<p><a href="http://itsamans.world/but-not-every-guy-is-married-with-kids" title="">But Not every guy is married with kids!</a></p>,<p>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~</p>,<p>The pictures in this article gave me a thought. This website will use advertising to keep the lights on. And we will make the ads content appropriate. We won’t put an ad for an iPad in a post about chain saws.</p>,<p>Anyway, the thought. Tools kits for kids. One of the most important things I think I missed as a kid was familiarity with proper tools and their uses, and mechanical experience. I learned much of it in the Navy and I am a self-taught furniture maker. But I’d have been much further ahead of the game as a young man if someone had mentored me in <em>any</em> of the trades.</p>,<p>So here are some suggestion for bringing kids into the trades in a fun way. By “playing” with your son or daughter, going through the motions of using play tools, you not only engage them in a learning activity, you create a bond around that activity.</p>,<h2>For the Toddler:</h2>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkUFv2zAMhe_7FYEPuqVWHDdxu6pDhwHtBgwdEGxXgZZoR4sluRRTL_v1c5QW2DuJj9SnB-rOdQQeF4lPA6picpb3t6tKjn8-7tH1e76t6nNRLDxQ70IeUIV8ry9D2UiG4jC40KsixGKRuW0ki3Rpk1FFWU5pGeAKPPyNYQk2nRKjvzLRlzO6R07ly6cd0qsz-AspuRhUJeVWNlUlngN-26mVeB6RgM-tR-QH-8R-EN-BDsg_BjCofu5EikeaT2AEYae40-wGAVbzaUQ1UrRHw3oOexBMYA5zau2s8sC_Iy0rKXzGjRl3CTuD-vOTMzzbHgOrz3L1UO--rBopILmQ_jfO9K9WYd3AWm5N3dZd09xsO7ttrjebFuR1C3Z9I9I-TvptUR0MCfNNHUcMSbugA056csHGSTEdUYw070abOERS6yzBjod3S8rNxkjR9m91l1Xcf1jMuisv_33_D-41rgQ" height="244"></iframe>,<p>I chose this kit because it had a good variety of tools and some hardware. It makes the use of the tools less abstract over time. It will be easier to keep a kid angaged by “fixing” lots of things in different ways.</p>,<p>HOWEVER!!!</p>,<p>If you are Harley guy, and there are lots of you out there, there’s always this kit:</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkctu2zAQRff5CkML7hxRjB05aZiiQR5NgSItjHZL0ORIZs2HMhxXdb--Mp0AvSvOneHhxfDGdagDzDIdPMhqdJa2143gw58PW3D9lq7F4lhUs6Cxd7EMyIq_16ehYmSDyXsXe1nFVM0Kd5PQAp7aaGRV12OeR32ug_6b4lzbfMgE4dykUE_oHijXrx_XgL-dgZ-A2aUoBectXwnBXiJ8WcuGvQyAmo6tJ6BP9jMFz75q3AF989qA_LFmOe1xOmnDEDpJnSLnmbaKDgPIAZPdG1JT2B0j1GY3pVbOyqDpV8K54CwU3FBwp7ATqD8-OcGLHSCSvOPN_dXq8eHqO9PZxfy_caQ_W7lcNBemaxZt25olF60A2Jh2IVYrvhTLlrO8TaN6W1SnfYZyU6UBYlYuqgijGl20aZSEe2ADTrtRJvmE8qKIkSP_bnF-eWk42_RvdVdU3Z7NJt3Up_--_Qea7q1M" height="244"></iframe>,<p>There’s not as many pieces, but damn! It’s a Harley kit!</p>,<p>Either way, by using toys like this, as well as doctor kits and crayons, you can immerse yourself in you own kid’s world. Let him imitate and then lead, go back and forth. If you are a first time father you will be amazed at what you learn about your son or daughter as you do this. And they will love you for it.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/what-is-a-man/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c533441e-bce8-4eb4-a4f5-53b1c3522dad</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 20:51:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[…But Not Every Guy is Married With Kids.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>…But Not Every Guy is Married With Kids.</h1>,<p><em><strong>“A man doesn't have time in his life<br> to have time for everything.<br> He doesn't have seasons enough to have<br> a season for every purpose. Ecclesiastes<br> Was wrong about that.”</strong></em></p>,<p>That’s an excerpt from the excellent poem <em>A Man in His Life</em> by Yehuda Amichai. It, among other works, are among the things all young men should read. It makes the clear point that life is about decisions and actions that must be taken, regardless of what life brings you.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e39a65d0-7d08-42ac-8e05-5b4c6fc2441b.jpg">,<p>A single man is every bit as burdened or blessed by these challenges as the married man. The idea that being single is a picnic is an illusion. While the partnered father may have the burden of protecting and providing for others, the motivation to do so is provided him, in that those people exist.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/52a83a83-fa03-46b3-b3eb-4529800580e8.jpg">,<p>The single man must make his life, and find success and maturity through his own motivation; under his own head of steam. If he makes excuses, he makes them to ether. He cannot measure success by the love and gratitude in the eyes of others. He can only measure it through harsh self-assessment.</p>,<p>Does he have greater freedom? Of course. But he has no counterweight to help him modulate how he enjoys that freedom. He only has his own ambition and his own conscience to guide him.</p>,<p>It is as a single man he should develop his passions. If his work is his passion, he is lucky indeed, but even that isn’t enough to round him out and allow him to make the most of his world. A few days hiking the Appalachian Trail or working wood into a desk or repairing a small engine will help him to take on his professional or trade challanges afresh for the following week.</p>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/95184b24843201b63240e7a992299c76/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=3426&cropwidth=4904&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fs3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fthe-grid-img%2Fp%2F9951dc6d9a6f3a243f620c09c929656abfedc806.jpg&x=30&y=0">,<p>And of course, unless he intends to remain single, he must balance his freedom and maneuverability against the possibility of attracting his soul mate. This is the hardest and most critical task of all.</p>,<p>Man Ironing</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxljtEKgjAYhV9leN9-XVNSTAyhq4heYa3pRrrJNpTevs3oIro88J3vnJs03qDOiofyFaoZklb0x0R6P7sKYF1X3I-KPy3mZoI50g7KoqBpVh7aa0qBlDQnGdnnJYWkOWlvlBaXD9kOE1NjrNbAGnTeTGhR7HcpDAVk7tUgfYSTpvvGrfd3i1vBvFpEYCejHTZ2gOAW2gkH99dO851jQHAaHnEeHW_zok1d" height="244"></iframe>,<p>Hoodie</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxlztEKwiAYBeBXkd3P39kijTWCQZfRK5hzU9pUVDZ6-9ygi-jywDkf56FdcqgLqjfpjBqBdFDDpdAp-XgGWNcVD5ORr4Clm8Fv7Qic8ZoSSq53QuBQsYqfas6ONRStdl5NKsaKsgZEi277GC1G_OLZzqAfzKjTRhdt94377u-JDEoks6jcnZ2N2IURsq1sVBGe79LK0vZAMcknpNyMD6BKR-s" height="244"></iframe>,<p>Man in a suit</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxlztEKgyAYBeBXke7n76xJRYtBsMuxV3BqKSsNlaK3nwW7GLs8cM7HeWoXHeq8kibWqOFIe9VfMx3jHGqAdV1xPxrx9li4Cea9HeBMqqJklyq_PQiFnDBWspJQWkDWcjmqDWu-rc7JBniL7sceLYb_-olP5tybQcddz9ruG4_d3xnhFY9mUak7ORuw8wMkW9mgAry2kxUnK4Fikm4IsRsfqjhJVA" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/but-not-every-guy-is-married-with-kids/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5d30d091-ca53-4364-9c90-f48add0fa411</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 20:52:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who We Are Here For…]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Who We Are Here For…</h1>,<p>This is a site for guys to get what guys want, from places they can relate to, and based on good information. And it’s about just being a guy.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/402c22d2-e86a-42d8-a150-882bfbefa289.jpg">,<p><em>Daddy like! In the world of home workshops this is what would be known as a wet dream.</em></p>,<p>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~</p>,<p>Someday soon you’ll be standing in your driveway, after work, talking to your neighbor.</p>,<p>You: <em>Yeah, went to Man’s World today. Bought a hyphendoophenator. Nice one. Three-speed, self-attenuating…all the bells and whistles.</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>Was the flux capacitor standard?</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Yep.</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>How good is the whodaddy attachment?</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Perfect!</em></p>,<p>Neighbor: <em>Damn. I got my hyphendoophenator at Lowe’s. The only thing it comes with is an automatic nose picker and a cup holder. And the whodaddy is made of plastic!</em></p>,<p>You: <em>Yeah, well, I told you to go to Man’s World, didn’t I?</em></p>,<p>We will create a page for you, where ever you are in the market, for anything we can find to make your life better. We’ll start with tools and add on from there. We will source information for the best stuff at different price points and feature them. We hope to save you a lot of headaches when buying. Did you catch that? I didn’t say shopping. Men don’t shop. They buy.</p>,<p>But you need good intel, and we will do our best to provide just that.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxlztEKgjAYBeBXGd63f2kpE5NA6DJ6g1jz143aJttQevuc0EV0eeCcj3NTLjrSeex1rEkjiPI4nDIV4xRqgGVZ6PDS8umpdAam1A7A-ZHzsijOV8agKit2yNk-Z5C1JlpEfzfCNiBactmmZNbil17llZsGPaqY4KztvnHb_f2QHkXUM65d42ygzo-w2mgDBni8d7aHnKYDUibgA4dIRto" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/who-we-are-here-for/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bc30ab32-0cd0-4bf1-bbbe-9a49ef208188</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 20:46:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tool Kits for K thru 5]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Tool Kits for K thru 5</h1>,<h2>CARPENTRY/WOODWORKING</h2>,<p>So your child isn’t a toddler anymore. If he enjoyed his first toy tool kit, you may consider upping the game a bit. I looked at what is on the market and these items jumped out at me.</p>,<p>Amazon sometimes shows them as a combination if you pull up the woodworking kit. This kit is amazing. I have three grandchildren, a girl and two boys, one featured in the post <em><a href="http://itsamans.world/what-is-a-man" title="">What Is A Man?</a>, </em>who will soon be ready for this. Shy of having your kids work in the shop on real projects (that could get a bit dodgy), I can’t think of a better way to teach them the basics.</p>,<p>Note: The younger they are the more you’ll have to remind them that tools and lumber can’t be left around. That’s “dangerous” and can ruin a good project. “Besides”, you might say, “This is how <em><strong>real</strong></em> carpenters take care of their stuff.”</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkU9vEzEQxe98imgPvqXr7rabUOoiEBIUCaVSBBIna2LPbkz8ZxlPWNJPz8ZpJd7J82b889P43vUEAReZTx5VNTnL-7vrRo5_3-3RDXu-a27ORbUIQIOLZUBV8rW-DBUjG0reuzioKqZqUbi7RBbp0iajqrqe8jLCFQR4TnEJNp8yY7gyKdQzekDO9e_3W6Q_zuAPpOxSVI2UK7luGrGJ-HWrrsVmRAI-tz4jf7BfOHjxDeiA_OTBoPq-FTkdaT6BEYS94l6z8wKs5tOIaqRkj4b1HPYgmMAc5tTaWRWAfyVaNlKEghsL7hJ2Bg3nJ2d4sQNGVh-lfPv489PqaSMgu5j_N870R6v6FladsXJ323fdykIHuGvbZn2z7kzTt7ci79OkXxbVg89Ybuo0YszaRR1x0pOLNk2K6YhipHk32iSfSLVFgh37V0vKrjNS7IaXui-qHt4sZt3Xl_9--Adve67E" height="244"></iframe>,<p>Here’s a tool kit that is an obvious step up from plactic hammers, but sized and designed for young hands.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkU1vGyEQhu_9FdYeuDmLiWPni1TppUmkypEs94owDGtiPrbDOBv313eNE6nviXlneHg13HuHOsKk0DGAbAZvaXc7E7z_uNuB73Z0K-anoplEjZ1PdUA2_Ks-D1WjGMwh-NTJJuVmUrnbjBbw3EYjm7YdyjTpCx3135ym2pZjIYgXJsd2RHdApf3zfQ347g38Biw-Jyk4X_JrIdgqwctaztiqB9R0av0EerRPFAP7pXEP9Bq0AblZs5IPOJ60YQhOklPkA9NW0bEH2WO2B0NqDLtnhNrsx9TKWxk1vWWcCs5ixfUVdw47grrTkyO82hESyR-czx6fN2KzYrr4VP43TvRnK831zeWNmAs7X7qrhbmyzjjuDOdiubWCa1Z2eVCfi3I6FKg3Ve4hFeWTSjCowSebB0l4ANbjuBtlcsgoL6sYeQpfFueLheFs233Wrqp5-DYZdd-e__vhH0y9rp4" height="244"></iframe>,<p>OR</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkU1vEzEQhu_8imgPvqXrLGibtHURcKBFgiJF9GpN7NmNiT-W8YQl_Hocp5UYX_y-M348Ht-5gSDgIvPJo2pmZ3l_s-rk9Od2j27c80337iyaRQAaXawFqpGv-lJUjWwoee_iqJqYmkXl7hJZpEuajGrads7LCFcQ4G-KS7D5lBnDlUmhLegRObe_3m-RfjuDz0jZpag6Ka_luuvEU8QvW7USTxMS8Dn1GfmDfeDgxVegA_J3DwbVj63I6UhlB0YQDooHzc4LsJpPE6qJkj0a1qXZg2ACcyhda2dVAP6ZaNlJESpuqrhLswU0nq8s8GoHjKw-SrnefHv89LAWkF3M_xtn-qNVIFfXG1lGurMb6LsiNqYsxJ0xfV9elfdp1i-DGsBnrCd1mjBm7aKOOOvZRZtmxXREMVGZjTbJJ1Jvawh27F8tKfveSLEbX_RQo7l_syhx117--_4f90auCw" height="244"></iframe>,<p>Why should I leave my baby girl out, right?</p>,<h2>Okay…Here’s a two-fer. Help spur their love of reading while teaching them how to use plans to execute successful projects.</h2>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkcFu2zAMhu97isAH3VIrauykXdWip7UFhg4IuqtAS7SjRZY8iamXPf0UpQXGE_mT-viDurN9hBEXiU4OZTVbQ_vbleDTn697tMOebsX6XFSLEeJgfRmQFf-sL0NFSDoG56wfZOVDtSjcLkSD8dKOWlZ1PaelhysY4W_wSzDplAjHKx3GOqMHpFT_fthhfLcaf2JMNngpON_wrRDs1ePLTq7Y64QR6Nz6hvRonmh07DvEA9IPBxrl246lcIw5A80i9pJ6RdYxMIpOE8opBnPUpLLZA6MI-pBdK2vkCPQrxKXgbCy4qeAuZjNoOK_M8CKP6Eny9bYVDW82KwbJ-vS_cKY_G9k1TStE291s4Rq2je70JqebFltYQ9fesLQPs_o4VA8uYXmpwoQ-KeuVx1nN1pswS4pHZFPMt1E6uBDldQlGltynxHnbas664aPuS1T3XxY57urLf9__A5EsrX0" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkU9vEzEQxe98imgPvqXr7rabUOoiEBIUCaVSBBIna2LPbkz8ZxlPWNJPz8ZpJd7J82b889P43vUEAReZTx5VNTnL-7vrRo5_3-3RDXu-a27ORbUIQIOLZUBV8rW-DBUjG0reuzioKqZqUbi7RBbp0iajqrqe8jLCFQR4TnEJNp8yY7gyKdQzekDO9e_3W6Q_zuAPpOxSVI2UK7luGrGJ-HWrrsVmRAI-tz4jf7BfOHjxDeiA_OTBoPq-FTkdaT6BEYS94l6z8wKs5tOIaqRkj4b1HPYgmMAc5tTaWRWAfyVaNlKEghsL7hJ2Bg3nJ2d4sQNGVh-lfPv489PqaSMgu5j_N870R6v6FladsXJ323fdykIHuGvbZn2z7kzTt7ci79OkXxbVg89Ybuo0YszaRR1x0pOLNk2K6YhipHk32iSfSLVFgh37V0vKrjNS7IaXui-qHt4sZt3Xl_9--Adve67E</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">64e8435a-73f7-4b57-ba80-020d09140873</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 02:55:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hobbies and Pursuits]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Hobbies and Pursuits</h1>,<h1>Photography</h1>,<p><a href="http://itsamans.world/the-eye-within-the-eye" title="">The Eye Within The Eye</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://itsamans.world/hobbies-and-pursuits/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a19f7c6d-a528-4c2f-9366-578e43b05784</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 21:21:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>